我琢磨着该给艾玛吃第一块饼干了
You know,I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
第一块？她常吃饼干
Her first cookie? She has cookies all the time.
我没喂过她饼干
I've never given her a cookie.
-你给她了？ -没有！
- Have you? - No.
另外，我也没从罐子里拿糖给她。
No. And for the record,I've also never given her frosting from a can.
瑞秋，领养中心要我们交一份推荐信。
Hey,Rach,the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation..
你愿意帮我们写一封吗？
and we wondered if you would write one for us?
-乐意效劳，我的荣幸 -谢谢
- Of course. I would be honored. - Thank you.
怎么不找我？
I think there's been an oversight.
乔伊，我们本想找你，但又觉得你可能没兴趣
We would have asked you. We thought you wouldn't be interested.
我们觉得你可能不擅长跟文字打交道
It's just that we don't think of you as really being so much with the words.
看样子我们错了
Clearly,we were wrong.
对于你们二位，我有很多好话可写
I got a lot of nice stuff to say about you guys,okay?
而且我也非常清楚你们多想要个宝宝
I know how much you want to have a baby..
我很想帮你们
and I would love to help you get one.
好吧，乔伊，你来写
You know what? Then we want you to do it.
谢谢，我想想怎么开头。
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
亲爱的婴孩领养权决定人：
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People.."
迫不及待想看你写的推荐信。
So excited about your letter.
-嘿！ -嘿！菲比！
- Hey. - Hey,Phoebe.
-你可真好看！ -没错，是很美
- Wow,don't you look nice. - Yes,I do.
今天麦克和我庆祝一周年。
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
什么的周年？
What's it the anniversary of?
第一次约会？第一次亲吻？第一次上床？
Your first date,your first kiss,first time you had sex?
对。
Yeah.
你们会去好地方隆重庆祝咯？
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
看尼克斯队比赛。
A Knicks game.
你好象穿得过于隆重？
Aren't you a little overdressed?
我从未和哪个男人有过一周年。
I've never had a one-year anniversary before..
所以不管去哪里庆祝，我一定要盛装打扮
so no matter where we go,I'm wearing something fancy..
带最好的珠宝
I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry..
还要在公共洗手间做爱
and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
是吗？
You guys do that?
钱德连在我家洗手间做爱也不肯
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
洗手间是尿尿的地方！
That's where people make number two.
瑞秋的妹妹带孩子
The.One.Where.Rachel's.Sister.Babysits
我有点时间，你想不想
So,you know,I have a little time if you want to..
好想，但是要给卷子评分
I'd love to,but I really have to grade these papers.
好，那好吧
Fine. It's fine.
那我就自己去洗澡
I'll just shower by myself.
“B”、"B"…
B,B,B,B,B
你给陶器目录也打了个"B"
You gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
他们有很好的创意。脱衣服吧
Well,it had some good ideas. Take off your shirt.
- 该死！ -开门，瑞秋，你妹妹来了。
- Damn it. - Rachel,open up! It's your sister!
我要谈谈
I have to talk to you.
嗨！艾美.
Hi,Amy.
克里斯蒂娜・艾伯盖特
Christina Applegate
-你不是瑞秋 -仍然牙尖嘴利
- You're not Rachel. - Still sharp as a tack.
查莉，这是瑞秋的妹妹艾美。艾美，这是查莉。
Charlie,this is Rachel's sister Amy. Amy,this is Charlie.
-很高兴认识你 -嗨！
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Hi,hi.
你是？
And you are?
罗斯，以前跟你们住一个街区
Ross? I grew up on your block?
去年我们一起吃感恩节大餐
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
我和你姐生了个孩子
I had a baby with your sister?
不，我…
No. I..
昨天我从你那儿买了中东三明治？
Did I buy a falafel from you yesterday?
没错
Yes. Yes,you did.
瑞秋，你妹妹艾美来了。
Hi,Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
她说我需要胸肌整形
She thinks I need pec implants.
艾美？嗨！
Amy? Hi.
-记得乔伊吗？ -当然
- You remember Joey. - Yeah. Hey,sure.
-《我们的日子》里的演员 - 对！
- The Days of our Lives guy. - That's right,yeah.
你演得真烂
You are not good.
见到影迷总是让人高兴
Always nice to meet a fan.
-你来干嘛？ -我有大新闻
- So,now,what are you doing here? - Well,I have huge news.
-抱歉，先看看孩子 -我有很重要的事，爱拉不能等等？
- Hold on. Let me check on the baby. - This is important. Can't Ella wait?
她名叫“艾玛”
Her name is Emma.
干嘛改名呀？爱拉好听多了！
Why did you change it? Ella was so much prettier.
我哪晓得，我只是推着小车卖中东小吃的罢了
What do I know? I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
你英文有长进
Hey,your English is getting better.
-天呐！ -对。
- Oh,my God. - I know.
她可能是我恨过的最辣的女孩
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
-你干嘛？ -莫妮卡和钱德的推荐信
- What you working on? - Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
我想让文字透着机灵劲 但深奥的词我又不会
I want it to sound smart,but I don't know any big words or anything.
-那你试试"词典" -我刚说了深奥的不会
- Why don't you use your thesaurus? - What did I just say?
看着
Watch.
选中想改的词
Here,highlight the word you want to change,go under "tools"..
在工具条找到"词典" 激活
and the thesaurus generates.. Gives.
“给出”供选词语表。
Gives a whole list of choices.
选一个更有学问的词，就行了
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
太好了！我变机灵了！
My God,that's great. I'm smart.
不，我变得
No,no,I'm:
“才华横溢”、“聪明伶俐” 我爱这软件
"Brainy,bright,clever." I love this thing!
各位，乔伊崔比亚尼重装上阵了！
Look out,ladies! Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
天呐！
God..
美极了！
so beautiful.
是啊，她好可爱
I know,isn't she?
不，我是说你的毯子
No,I was talking about your bedding.
艾美，你要说什么新闻？
All right,what's your news,Amy?
呃…
Well..
我要结婚了
I'm getting married.
天呐！
Wow! Oh,my God!
- 和谁结婚？ - 一个男人
- To who? - This guy.
他的房子太爽了
He has a killer apartment.
-还有呢？ -在第五大道
- And..? - And it's on Fifth.
电梯开门就到起居室
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
-他人如何？ -还行
- No,what's he like? - Oh,he's okay.
还记得我以前的男朋友马克吗？
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
-记得 -我要嫁他的父亲
- Yeah. - It's his dad.
-那他可… - 太老了?对
- Wow,so he's gotta be.. - Old? Yeah.
但他常常旅行，不怎么待在家
But he travels a lot,so he's hardly ever there.
你好象更喜欢他的房子
Sweetie,I gotta tell you,it sounds a little bit like..you like the apartment
胜过...？
more than you like..
马瑞.
Myron.
说过他年纪大嘛
Yeah,I told you he was old.
坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
宝贝，你知道吗
Honey,you know..
我也曾差一点嫁给一个我不爱的人
I once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
-记得贝瑞吗？ -记得？
- Do you remember Barry? - Remember him?
你睡了以后我们常一起鬼混
God,we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
有时点头回答就够了
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
不管怎么样，听着
But anyway,listen.
不嫁贝瑞，是我一生最英明的决定
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever,ever made.
亲爱的，你应该得到真爱 你的另一半就在某处
Honey,Amy,you deserve true love. Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
一个同龄人，聪明而有趣，你也爱他
Someone that is your age,that is smart,that is fun..
在乎他
and that you care about.
没错。
You're right.
-没错。就这么干 - 好！
- You're right. I'm gonna do it. - Okay.
我要嫁给马瑞，再接着找我的另一半
I'm gonna marry Myron and keep looking for Mr. Right.
接着说吧
Okay,let's keep talking.
请让让，我们过周年
Excuse me. Anniversary.
先生，请把玉米片挪挪 这是我的位子
Sir,could you move your nachos? They're in my seat.
我们过周年
It's my anniversary.
一年了
Here we are.
-真不敢相信 -是啊
- I can't believe it's been a whole year. - I know.
这是最好的一年
This has been the best year..
-我一辈子最快乐的一年！ -我也是！
- This has been the best year of my life! - Me too!
从不知道会如此爱一个人！
I never thought I could love someone this much!
我有同感！
I feel the same way!
你慷慨又高尚，善良，床上又好厉害！
You're so generous and kind,and you're amazing in bed!
我们在庆祝周年
It's our anniversary.
尼克队的球迷们，请看亮分牌大屏幕这边。
Knicks fans,please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
有人要问一个很特别的问题
Someone has a special question to ask.
（朱莉，你愿意嫁给我吗？）
老套！俗气！丢人现眼！
How lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
-真的吗？ -这是最不好的求婚方式！
- Really? - It's the worst way to propose.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
请看我写的推荐信
I finished my recommendation. Here.
你们一定会高兴得不得了
And I think you'll be very,very happy.
从来没这么久盯着电脑，居然没去看色情网站的
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer without looking at porn.
看不懂
I don't understand.
是不是有些词对你来说有点太深奥？
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
根本没有任何意思
It doesn't make any sense.
哦，当然，我太聪明了，我查了词典
Well,of course it does. It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
每个词都用？
On every word?
没错
Yep.
这句话原本是什么意思？
All right,what was this sentence originally?
他们是热心的好人
"They are warm,nice people with big hearts."
结果变成：他们是潮湿的 给人好感的智人人类
And that became,"They are humid,prepossessing Homo sapiens..
具有标准尺寸的心脏大动脉
with full-sized aortic pumps."
我真心这么想
Yeah. Yeah. And hey,I really mean it,dude.
乔伊，恐怕我们不能用这封信
All right,Joey,I don't think we can use this.
-为什么？ -因为你的签名是：
- Why not? - Well,because you signed it:
袋鼠宝宝：崔比亚尼 （有一个卡通袋鼠形象叫乔伊）
"Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani."
算了，你还是不要假装有学问 就用你的本色来写怎么样？
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart and just be yourself.
你不必用词典，要用“心”写
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
让它发自你的标准尺寸的心脏大动脉？
Your full-sized aortic pump.
- 艾美！嗨！ -我听了你的话
- Amy. Hi. - I took your advice.
-我跟马瑞分手了。 -太好了
- I left Myron. - Good for you!
是啊，简直像艾琳布劳克维奇（《永不妥协》的女主角，很坚强的女性）
I know. I'm Erin Brockovich.
对。
Yes,you are.
-以你为荣 - 谢谢
- I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
我能住你这里吗？
So can I stay with you?
艾琳布劳克维奇有自己的家
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
看谁又来啦
Look who's back.
你怎么带行李？ 她为什么带行李？
Why do you have bags? Why does she have bags?
我要和你们住一块了
I'm staying with you guys.
- 什么？ -我们是同居室友了！
- What? - We're gonna be roomies!
来。
Come on.
-你睡在外面？ - 是啊！
- You slept out here? - Yeah.
她梦中把我踢出来 还叫嚣什么：马瑞，滚出去！
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep,yelling,"Myron,get off!"
我们会把她赶走对吧？ 答应我，赶走她
But we're getting rid of her,right? Please tell me we're getting rid of her?
-我下不了手，乔伊 -噢,不会吧.
- Joey,I can't do that. - Oh,come on.
昨晚我刚吃完一半披萨，她就说
Last night I was finishing off a pizza,and she said:
嘴上爽一把，屁股胖一生
"A moment on the lips,forever on the hips."
在我家不许说这种话！
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
乔伊，我知道她难相处
Joey,look,I know that she's difficult..
但她来这里也不错
but I think it's really good that she's here.
这样她滚蛋后我们才能更欢喜？
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
我刚搬来还不是一样
No,it's just.. Look,when I first moved to this city,I was a lot like her.
被惯坏，自我中心 你们几个却照顾我
I was spoiled,self-centered. And you guys really took care of me.
是莫妮卡强迫我们
Yeah. Monica made us.
不管怎样我都很感激
Well,whatever. I really appreciate it..
如果没有你们
because I don't think I would be the person I am today..
也就没有现在的我
if it wasn't for you guys.
我想帮帮艾美，就像你们帮我那样
So I want to help Amy the way you guys helped me.
我知道这需要极大的耐性，我可以
And I know it's gonna take patience,but that's okay.
-早 -是的
- Good morning. - Yeah.
艾美，那是我今天要穿的衣服 所以我才挂在门上。
That's what I'm wearing today. That's why I hung it on the door.
宝贝，你总不能给我扒下来
Oh,sweetie,you can't pull this off.
你知道吗，现在我们也许应当坐下来
You know what? I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time..
好好谈谈你的将来
for us to sit down and,you know,talk about your future.
我没空，我要去修眉
Oh,I can't,honey. I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
这样的眉毛我不快乐
I am not happy.
你真要吃吗？
Sure you want to eat that?
我就是想增加曲线美，我喜欢！
I'm curvy and I like it!
-嗨！ -嗨！
- Hi. - Hi.
最烂的周年庆！
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
才不是呢 莫妮卡，给她讲讲我们去年怎么过的周年
I doubt that. Tell her about us last year.
我给钱德买了一只500元手表。 而他，给我写了首饶舌歌。
Well,I bought Chandler a $500 watch,and he wrote me a rap song.
-真的？ -是..
- Seriously? - Word.
我的比你还逊
Mine was worse than that.
-怎么啦？ -球赛时
- Well,what happened? - We were at the game.
有人在大屏幕上求婚
This guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
-老套！ -我也是那么说
- That is so tacky. - Well,that's what I said.
结果呢，原来麦克昨晚上就想用 这种方式向我求婚！
But it turns out Mike was planning to propose to me that same way last night.
天哪，麦克要求婚？
Oh,my God. Mike was gonna propose?
-真是大件事！ -你想嫁给他吗？
- That's huge. - Do you want to marry him?
当然想啦！
Yeah,I really do. Yes.
结果我那句话把他堵回去了
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna do it..
我想他一辈子都不会求婚了。 在巴贝多我拒绝过他一次了，现在又
I don't think he'll ever ask again. I said no in Barbados,and now this?
没错。如果我是男人
She's right. If I were a guy and..
我刚才是不是说： 如果我是男人？
Did I just say,"If I were a guy"?
别等他求婚了，主动出击吧
You don't need him to propose to you. Maybe you could propose to him.
哦，不知道，我又不是想嫁想疯了
Oh,I don't know. I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
我向钱德求的婚
I proposed to Chandler.
好吧，继续
All right,moving on.
我不觉得你想嫁想疯了，我觉得你很棒
I don't think it was desperate. It was amazing.
谢谢。
Thank you.
-你们都认为我该求婚？ -那一定很棒
- Well,do you think I should propose? - I think it could be kind of great.
当然！世上再没有比求婚更美妙的感觉了！
Absolutely. You'll love the feeling. There's nothing like it.
好，那我应该怎么办
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
在球赛的大屏幕上告白
How about at a game on the big screen?
更老套的求婚方式如何？
How about at a Foot Locker?
他既然选择过大屏幕求婚，可见他能接受这种方式
What? What,he obviously thinks that's a nice way to be proposed to.
-而且他也不会起疑心 -有理
- Plus,he'd never suspect it. - Yeah,that does make sense.
-你们会喜欢吗？ -我喜欢
- Okay,now,would you two like that? - Sounds good to me.
不过男性会怎么想？
But what would a guy think?
-奶奶的电话 - 哇！
- Nana's on the phone. - Wow.
有趣，她七年前就死了
That's interesting,since she died seven years ago.
是吗？
She did?
那她在博卡的房子归谁了？
Who got her condo in Boca?
喂
Hello?
是我们的保姆
It's our nanny.
喂
Hi.
是吗，希望你早点康复。再见
Oh,God,I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是莫莉，她病了
That's Molly. She's sick.
-今天你看孩子可以吗 -不行， 我要连堂上课
- Can you watch Emma today? - I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
莫莉说她生什么病？我的喉咙也不舒服
Did Molly say what she had? Because my throat's been hurting.
痛经
Menstrual cramps.
我可能不是这毛病
I don't think that's what this is.
-你们帮忙看着艾玛成吗？ -抱歉，亲爱的
- Can any of you watch Emma? - No,I'm sorry,sweetie.
我要上班，还要求婚
No,I've got work,and then I'm proposing.
那怎么办
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
我可以帮手
Well,I could do it.
-好 -可以跟你谈一谈吗？
- Well,actually.. - Can I talk to you for a second?
我不赞成让她看孩子
I do not want her babysitting our child.
-为什么？ -首先，她老是把我们的孩子喊成“爱拉”
- Why not? - For one thing,she keeps calling her Ella.
-这名字也不错嘛 -好，下一胎叫"爱拉"
- Ella's a nice name. - Fine,we'll call the next one Ella.
-下一胎？ - 好
- The next one? - Okay.
我不赞成她帮我们看孩子
I don't want her watching our baby.
我只是想改造她
Ross,I am trying to help her become a better person.
这是个好机会
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
可以教她为别人做点事
She just offered to do something for another human being.
我不懂
You know,I don't know.
罗斯，我是说
Ross,I'm telling you..
她宁愿牺牲修眉的时间看孩子
she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this,all right?
这件事对我们意义重大！
Do you understand how important that is in our world?
我不小心听到你们的谈话。 因为我故意要听的
Listen,I couldn't help but overhear,because I was trying to.
就让我带孩子吧，我真心想帮你们
Listen,let me do this. I really want to help you guys out.
而且，瑞秋对我太好了
And plus,Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
-好！ -太好了!
- Absolutely. - Oh,great!
付多少工钱？
So how much does it pay?
乔伊，二稿如何？
How's the second draft of the letter coming?
完成了，事实上我已经寄出去了
Great. I'm finished. In fact,I just dropped it off at the agency.
-寄出去了？ -是啊。
- You dropped it off? - Yeah.
我们能读读吗？再打印一份给我们如何？
Can we read it? Can you print out another copy?
恐怕不行，朋友（西班牙语）
No can do,amigo.
我没用电脑，是手写的，显得更亲切
No,I didn't use the computer. It felt more personal to handwrite it.
-你手写？ -别担心
- You handwrote it? - Yeah,and don't worry.
我根本没有装得很聪明
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
再见
See you later.
天哪，信快寄到了。
Oh,my God. Oh,my God. That letter is gonna go in our file.
我们没指望了
We're never gonna get a kid.
我们会孤独终老
We're gonna be one of those old couples..
养花弄鸟
that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
别急
It's okay. You know what?
我打电话给领养中心 请他们扔掉那封信
I will just call the agency and tell them to throw out the letter.
好。
Okay,good.
喂，我是钱德宾
Hello,this is Chandler Bing.
有人手写了一封推荐信
Someone just dropped off a handwritten recommendation letter and..
好
Okay.
谢谢，再见
Thank you. Goodbye.
我们完蛋了对吗
We're screwed,aren't we?
先去买鸟，路上说给我听
You know what? Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
-他们喜欢那封信 -什么？
- They loved it. - What?
他们说我们很聪明，叫个小孩写推荐信
They thought it was very smart of us to have a child write the letter.
他们以为乔伊是小孩？
They thought Joey was a child?
他们看了他的画，以为他只有八九岁
She guessed 8,9,based on his drawings.
- 嗨！ -嗨！你们今天干嘛了？
- Hi. - Hey,what'd you guys do today?
爱拉想上街，所以我们去购物 还买了寿司
Ella wanted to go out,so we went shopping and got some sushi.
-有趣 -也不是啦
- That sounds like fun. - Yeah,not really.
宝宝很无趣
Babies are dull.
-我女儿怎样了？ -我很好
- Hey. Hi,how's my girl? - I'm fine.
我给你买了礼物，感谢你收留我
And I got you a present for letting me stay with you.
-准备好了？ - 嗯！
- Ready? - Yeah.
你给她穿了耳洞？
You pierced her ears?
她的鼻子看来小点了吗？
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
你给她穿了耳洞？
You pierced her ears?
竟然不征求我同意？
How could you do this without telling me?
我若先告诉你，就不是惊喜了
If I had told you,then it wouldn't have been a surprise,now would it?
我想她看来很可爱
I think she looks cute.
但我错了
But I am wrong.
天哪，罗斯会发飚的
Oh,my God. Oh,my God. Here comes Ross. He's gonna flip out.
中东女孩不能穿耳洞吗？
Why,did something happen to his falafel cart?
- 嗨，各位！. - 罗斯！
- Hey,guys. - Ross!
嗨，艾玛。 她的帽子干嘛压这么低？
Hi,Emma. Why is she wearing her hat so low?
-她都看不见了 -我不想让她看
- She can barely see. - I don't really want her to see.
为什么？
Why not?
因为世界上有太多可怕的事情了
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
有战争，还有乔伊冰箱里的那些东西
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
一只牛奶盒，但看来像块肉
It was in a milk carton,but it looked like meat?
快来，快来
Come here. Come here.
看她多乖
There she is. Hi.
-怎么啦？ -没什么
- What? - Nothing.
嗨！
Hi.
什么?
What..?
-那是夹上去的？ -是戴上的
- Please tell me those are clip-ons! - Oh,they're real.
是她干的？
Did she do this to her?
我早说过不能把艾玛交到她手上！
I told you we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
我知道了！你说得对
I know,I know. And you were right,Ross.
你太不负责了！ 绝不再让你看孩子！
Okay? You are so irresponsible! I am never letting you babysit again!
你们知道吗？ 她需要我！
You know what? This kid needs me,okay?
-她需要一个又酷又有趣的阿姨！ -我就是！
- She needs to have a cool,fun aunt. - I'm a cool,fun aunt.
好吧
Okay.
莫妮卡本来就是又酷又有趣，而且家务有条有理！
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun at organized indoor projects.
我只不过想帮你想清楚你将来想干什么！
All I wanted to do was help you try to figure out what to do with your life.
结果呢，这就是你给我的答案？
This is how you repay me?
谁稀罕你帮忙。我自己想好了
I don't need you to help me. I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
-是吗？几时想好的？ -今天
- Oh,yeah? Since when? - Since today.
我要当宝宝时尚专家！
I am going to be a baby stylist.
-啊？ -有这职业吗？
- What? - That's not a thing!
应该有！
Well,it should be.
我要教宝宝如何穿戴
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize..
选衣裳的颜色，什么衣服较瘦身
what colors to wear,what clothes are slimming.
-宝宝才不想苗条呢！ -如何像艾美一样美！
- Babies don't care if they're slim! - Enter Amy.
- 艾美,我要… -你想怎样？
- Amy,I.. I just.. I just wanna.. - What? What are you gonna do?
让你永远没有中东三明治吃！
No more falafel for you!
比赛很精彩
Great game,huh?
-你怎么老盯着大屏幕？ -没，我在祷告
- Why do you keep looking at the screen? - I'm not. I'm praying.
请让尼克队赢吧
Please let the Knicks win.
谢谢！托尔(北欧神话中的雷神)
Thank you,Thor.
-你上哪儿？ -卫生间
- Where are you going? - I'm going to the bathroom.
-等一会 -为什么？
- Well,I think you should wait. - Why?
如果不憋一会儿，你就无法摄取所有养分
Well,if you don't hold it in,you don't get all the nutrients.
尼克队的球迷，请注意积分牌大屏幕
Knicks fans,please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
（麦克，你愿意娶我吗）有人要问特别的问题
Someone has a special question to ask.
麦克哈尼根，娶我好吗？
Mike Hannigan,will you marry me?
看啊，她向他求婚！
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
我们猜一下这个家庭谁没种呢？
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
不要误导观众！
Well,that's not very enlightened.
嘘我们？嘘你们！
Boo us? Boo you!
奥丁（众神之父）将要惩罚你们！
Odin will smite you!
喂？我就是乔伊崔比亚尼
Hello? Yeah,this is Joey Tribbiani.
哦，嗨！
Oh,hi.
真高兴你喜欢我的信
Well,I'm glad you liked my letter.
我爹O、妈咪不在家
No,my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
再见
Okay,bye-bye.
她真慈祥
She was nice.
乔伊，把艾美的箱子拿出来，她要搬走了
Joey,get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
-你把妹妹踢出家门？ -你给我的宝宝穿耳洞！
- You're kicking me out? - You put holes in my baby's ears.
不然大家怎么知道她是女孩？
At least now people will know she's a girl!
不敢相信，我竟然想过要帮你！
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
-你不可救药！ - 你知道吗？
- You are so beyond help! - You know what?
这次见面你在否定我的一切！
Ever since I got here,you have been nothing but negative.
-你说什么？ -你不准我…
- Excuse me? - You didn't want me..
嫁有豪宅的老头
to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
我想帮你把你女儿的鼻子变小点
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws..
结果吃力不讨好？
and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
-乔伊，行李怎么还没搬出来？ -她的破玩意太多了
- Joey,where are those bags? - She has a lot of crap!
我刚搬来时，还憧憬姐妹团聚
You know? When I moved in here,I thought,"This will be so great.
像童年那样
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
而且没有该死的吉尔捣乱
Except without that stupid Jill.
顺便说一下，她变肥了
Who has gotten fat,by the way.
真的？
Seriously?
妈说吉尔肥了15磅
Mom said she gained,like,15 pounds.
-屁股和大腿长肉了？ -屁股和脸
- Hips or thighs? - Ass and face.
天啊，她不是节食吗？
Oh,my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
本来是，后来被男人甩了
She was. Carbs found her.
看，这才像姐妹
See? This is what I wanted.
真心交谈
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
哦，我可以这样
Oh,I can give you that.
- 你可以？ - 是的。
- You can? - Yeah.
我老想改造你。实际上
I kept trying to make you a better person,but you're..
你本来就接近完美了
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
谢谢你
Thank you.
必须承认，艾玛真可爱
You gotta admit,Emma does look cute.
-你刚说“艾玛”？ -对不起， 是爱拉
- Did you just say,"Emma"? - Oh,I'm sorry. Ella.
姐姐,你要给吉尔带意大利面吗?
Sis,you wanna go bring Jill some pasta?
艾美.那样做不好.
Come on,Amy. Now,that's just wrong.
她真正怕的是大蒜奶油面包片.
Her true weakness was garlic bread.
赛场里那家伙真是乱讲
That woman didn't know what she was talking about,Mike.
你当然有种
Obviously,you have balls.
-忘了算了 -你能忘了最好
- Please,let's forget the whole thing. - I would love it.
- 已经忘了 - 谢谢
- Consider it forgotten. - Thank you.
不管你何时、以何方式求婚
But just so you know..
我保证答应
However and whenever you decide to propose,I promise I'll say yes.
不管是篮球赛
Whether,you know,it's at a basketball game..
还是写在空中
or in skywriting..
或是像有部烂电影里的蹩脚男
or,you know,like some lame guy in a cheesy movie..
把戒指藏在蛋糕里
who hides it in the cake.
现在就在蛋糕里对吧？
It's in the cake,isn't it?
没种的男人还会有什么好点子吗
Where else would lame Mr. No Balls hide it?
我是怎么了？怎么老提这个！
What's the matter with me? Why do I keep ruining this?
-对不起嘛 -是我错
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - No,it's my fault.
我老用愚蠢的方式求婚
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways..
我只是想告诉你 我爱你，我想和你过余生
and I just wanna tell you I love you,and I wanna spend my life with you..
-我现在求婚 -天啊
- I'm gonna do this now. - Oh,my God.
-菲比 -暂停
- Phoebe,I.. - Wait. Oh,wait.
暂停
Oh,no.
好了。
Okay.
可以了？
Ready? Okay.
菲比，我爱你。
Phoebe,I love you.
世界上再也没有第二个女人会让我求婚三次
There's no one else in the world I would ask to marry me three times.
我想照顾你
But I want to take care of you..
和你生儿育女
have babies with you..
一起变老
and grow old with you.
菲比布菲，你愿意嫁我吗
Phoebe Buffay,will you marry me?
我愿意！
Yes.
-我爱你 -我爱你更多
- I love you. - I love you more.
不可能
Not possible.
她是“没种夫人”了
She's gonna be Mrs. No Balls!
“宝宝时尚专家”好当吗？
So how's the baby-styling business going?
行情不大好
Not that great.
好象大家都不爱听见他们的宝宝丑之类的话
It's almost as if people don't want to hear that their babies are ugly.
真让人吃惊
That's shocking.
那不是罗斯吗？罗斯！！！
There's Ross. Hey,Ross.
你好，罗斯！
Hello,Ross?
真没教养
He's rude.